You've got your sights set on taking your business global and reaching more
customers, but don't know where to start.
In this step, we'll cover the things you
should consider when deciding where and what to sell in Amazon's global
marketplaces.
First, do some research on your potential customers.
Amazon has
marketplaces in North America, Europe, and Asia, each with different customer
preferences, cultures, and languages.
It's important to understand what those
customers need and how you can tailor your product to meet those needs.
Next,
decide what to sell.
This includes making sure your product works in that
country and that you're compliant with all local taxes, regulations, and laws.
Amazon has services that can help manage those details for you, making the global
selling journey that much easier.
With a little thought and help from Amazon global
selling, you can be open for business all over the world in no time.